Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1879-1948; 121.0 boxes
  - Subseries 2A: General, 1885-1948; 101.0 boxes
    - Huebsch, B. W., Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Hughes & Muller, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Hughes, Rupert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Hull, Amy E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Hull, Lewis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Hull, Ralph G. P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Hulst, Mrs. Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Humphreys, Harry R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Hunt, Edith Holman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Hunt, Emily G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Hunt, Thelma [Mrs. Thomas Hunt], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Hunt, Thornton, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Hunter College, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Huntington, Archer W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Huntington, Philip, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Hurley, William L. Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Hurd, Charles S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Hurlburt, Mr., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Hurlong, H. P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Hurst, Kate, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Hurst, W. J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Huster, P. William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Hutchin, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Hutchinson, Arthur Emlen, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Hutchinson, C. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Hutkin, H. J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Hyde, James Tillotson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Idell, Albert E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Iles, George, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Immigrant Publication Society, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - The Independent, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Independent Fusion Campaign Committee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Independent New Jersey Cranberry Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Independent Republican Committee of Thirth-Five, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Independent Republicans, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Indian Rights Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Informal Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Ingersoll, Charles E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Ingersoll, Ernest, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Ingersoll, Raymond V., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Ingersoll, Robert Sturgis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Ingersoll, [Walton/Alton], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Ingham, James, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Ingham, John Hall, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Innes & Sons, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - The Inquirer, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Institute of American Genealogy, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - The Inter-Church Federation of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Intercollegiate Bureau of Occupations, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21a)
    - International Art Publishing Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - International Arts and Letters, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - International Book Review, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - International Nickel Company, 1910-1939; 2.0 folders (Folder 25-26)
    - International Studio, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Inter-State Fair, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - "Invention and Intervention", dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Invitations and calling cards--misc, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Irving, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Irwin, Alfred, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Irwin, Ellen D. [Mrs. James Irwin], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Irwin, Sophia Dallas & T. A. Irwin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Isham, Samuel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - The Item, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - [Iveigley], M. Furney, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Ives, F. E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Ives, Halsey C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Ives, Halsey C.--Jamestown Exposition and American Exposition--Guildhall, London and Dublin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - J. B. Lippincot Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - J. C. Penny Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - J. P. Morgan & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Jaccaci, August F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Jackson Day Dinner, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Jackson, J. S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Joseph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Lucy [Mrs. Albert Jackson], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Malcom, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Jackson, Samuel Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Jacques, Camille, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Jacob Reed's Sons, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Jacob, Robert, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Jacobs, George W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Jacobs, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Jacobs, Mary C. R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Jacoby, Douglas P. A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Jaffola, Adolph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - James, Anna C. [Mrs. H. B. James], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - James, Arthur Curtiss, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - James, Arthur H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - James, H. Lamb Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - James, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - James, T. White, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Jameson, G. L. S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Jamestown and Newport Ferry Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Jamestown and Newport Transfer Express Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Jamestown Board of Tax Assessors, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Jamestown Board of Trade, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Bridge Commission, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Bridge--Projected, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Chief of Police, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Clerk's Office, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Jamestown Colored Church, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Council President, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Jamestown Historical Society, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Improvement Society, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Volunteer Fire Department, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Jamestown Garage, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Postmaster, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Proposed Race Track, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Jamestown (R. I.) Tax Collector, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Janney, Susan W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Janvier, Meredith, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Japan Paper Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Jarvis, Anna, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Javis, M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Jastrow, Annie N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Jastrow, Helen, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Jastrow, Joseph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Jastrow, Morris, 1885-1921; 2.0 folders (Folder 1-2)
    - Jawer's Auto Supply Store, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Jay, George E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Jay, Oakley, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Jayne, Caroline, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Jayne, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Jayne, Henry Le Barre, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Jayne, Horace H. F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Jefferson Day Celebration, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Jefferson Hospital, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Jellet, Edwin C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Jenkins, Charles Francis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Jenkins, Howard M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Jenkintown Bank and Trust Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Jennewein, C. Paul, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Jennings, H. H. Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Jennings, Joseph M. Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Jensen, George, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Jerrehian Brothers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Jessup, Alexander, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Jewett, Sarah Orne, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Jitney Players, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Johansen, Jean McLane, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - John C. Winston Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - John G. Johnson Collection, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - John Lane Publishers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - John Wanamaker, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - John Wanamaker Competitive Art Exhibit, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Alba B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Johnson, Alexander H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Johnson, Amandus, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Johnson & Towers, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Johnson, Edward H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Johnson, Edwin Hine, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Johnson, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Emory R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Johnson, F. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Johnson, Frances Earle, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Johnson, J. D. Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Johnson, John G, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Johnson, Katherine, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Johnson, S. E. & Jeannie K. Johnson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Johnson, Mary E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35a)
    - Johnson, Sally W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Johnson, W. Martin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Johnson, Bertha, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Johnson, Frances Benjamin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Johnson, J. D. Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Johnson, M. F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Jones, B. Griffith, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Jones, C. S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Jones, Enid Daniel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Jones, E. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Jones, Francis C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Jones, Francis D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Jones, Frank Bowne, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Jones, Ida, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Jones, J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Jones, Lawrence E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Jones Library, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Jones, Louis C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Jones, M. E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Jones, M. L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Jones, Marion Corrine, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Jones, Rufus M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Jones, Thomas S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - Jones William Safford, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Jordon, David Starr, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Jordon, John W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Jordon, Wilfred, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Joseffy, Carl, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Joseph F. Guffey Primary Committee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Jost, Laurence C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Juillard School of Music, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Julia Ward Howe Public School, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Juniata College, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Justic, Theodore, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Kachelmacher, N. L. C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Kahn, Charles, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Kahn, Otto, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Kallen, Horace, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Kane, Florence Bayard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Kaplan, Sylvia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Karolik, Maxim, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Karsner, David, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Kates, Clarence Sears, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Kauffman & Cowell, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Kauffman, Reginald Wright, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Kaufman, Augustus, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Kaull, James Turner, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Kay, Gertrude A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Keator, Anna [Mrs. John Frisbee Keator], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Keeler, L. M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Keeley, Robert N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Keen, Florence, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Keen, W. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Keene & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Keith, Ellen, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Keith, Elsie Wister, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Keller, Arthur, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Keller, Francis Pike, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34a)
    - Keller, Frederick E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Kelley, Edgar Stillman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Kelley, Jane M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Kelley, Margaret, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Kelly, Charles, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Kelly, George F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder [40])
    - Kelly, John B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Kelly, Philip F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Kelly, R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Kelsey, Albert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Kelsey, Charles C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Kelwey, A. Clinton, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Kendall, Margaret, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Kendall, William Sergeant, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Kendrick, W. Freeland, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Keneseth Israel Sisterhood, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Kennedy & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Kennedy, C. Rann, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Kennedy, David E., Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Kennedy, David Edwards, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Kennedy, E. G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Kennedy, Frank G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Kennedy, Frederick P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Kent, Dorthea, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - Kent, R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Kent, Rockwell, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 60)
    - Kent, S. Leonard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 61)
    - Kent, Samuel L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 62)
    - Kephart, John W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 63)
    - Kepriotes & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 64)
    - Ker, Mrs. N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 65)
    - Keratry Emile de, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 66)
    - Kerlin, Robert T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 67)
    - Ketterlinus Lithographic Manufacturing Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 68)
    - Keyes, Grace D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 69)
    - Keyes, Lillian G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 70)
    - Keyser, Cassius J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 71)
    - Keystone Marine Motor Works, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 72)
    - Kibbe, Harrie G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Kiefer, Daniel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Kimball, H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Kind, Morris J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Kindleberger, E. Crosby, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - King, Charles, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - King, Clarence, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - King, James W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - King-McLeod Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - King, Wyncie, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Kingdon, Mona, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - King's Battery and Auto Electric Service Station, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Kingsbury, Mable G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Kinsolving, Sally Bruce, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Kipling, Rudyard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Kirby, Ellwood R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Kirby, Thomas E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Kirk, Ellen Olney, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Kirk, John Foster, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Kirk, Sophia (The Misses Kirk's School), dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Kirk, Stuart L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Kirkbridge, Franklin B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Kirschbaum School of Languages, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Kitson, Ernest, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - The Kittatinny, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Kittredge, Herman E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Klauder, Charles Z., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Klein, L. Ruth Murray, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Klein, P. M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Kling, Flora Gardner, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Knapp, Glibert P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Knauff, Theo C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Knerr, Melitta Herring, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Knight, Emil G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Knoedler, M & Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Knowles, A. C. & Louise Knowles, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Knox, Frank, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Knox, John S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Knox, Mary F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Knudsen, John, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Kohn, Irving, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Kolah Grotto, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Kolb, Louis J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Kondo, Eizo, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Kondle, Burton Alva, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Konti, J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Koopman, Augustus, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Korman, Hyman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Koropal, Henry William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Kraemer, Edmund M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Kratzer, Alfred, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Kraus, Louis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Kreider, Charles D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Kriebel, Henry S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Kroll, Leon, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Kronberg, Louis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Krux, [M.], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Kuehnle Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - [Kugeman], Katherine Johnson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Kuhn, C. Hartman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 60)
    - Kunz, George F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 61)
    - [Kurschbum], Benno, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 62)
    - Kurtz, Charles M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 63)
    - Kurtz, Charles R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 64)
    - Kurtz Hooked Rug Makers, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 65)
    - KYW Radio Station, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 66)
    - L. A. Nagle & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - L. F. Seyfet's Sons Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - L. J. Mueller Furnace Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - L. R. Hamersly & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - LaFarge, Bancel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - LaFarge, C. Grant & Florence B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - LaFarge, John, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - LaFollette, Robert M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - LaMarche & Coady, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - LaWall, Charles H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Lacian, S. L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Lacy, Ernest, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)